Anthony Lewis Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Annual File, 1949-2007 (Box II:1-843)
  - 1993
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Free speech, (3 folders)
    - Fund for Free Expression
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Gay rights, (2 folders) (Box II:551)
    - Gideon's Trumpet, (3 folders)
    - Great Britain
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Trip
    - Guinier, Lani, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:552)
    - "G" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Haiti, (2 folders)
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., (1 folder) (Box II:553)
    - Health, (6 folders)
    - Hersey, John
    - Human rights
      - East Timor
      - General, (2 folders) (Box II:554)
    - "H" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Immigration
    - Iran
    - Iran-Contra Affair
    - Iraq, (2 folders)
    - Ireland, (2 folders)
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:555)
    - Kennedy, John F.
    - Kennedy, Robert F.
    - "K" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Latin America
      - Cuba
      - El Salvador, (3 folders)
      - General (Box II:556)
      - Guatemala
      - Panama
    - Law
    - Lydon, Christopher
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Mexico
      - General
      - Trip
    - Middle East
      - Egypt
      - General, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:557)
      - Palestine Liberation Organization
      - Peace, (3 folders)
      - Syria
      - United States
      - West Bank
    - "M" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:558)
    - National Security Archive
    - North American Free Trade Agreement
    - New York Times
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Magazine article, (2 folders)
      - Staff, (2 folders)
    - "N" miscellaneous (Box II:559)
    - Obscenity, (2 folders)
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Perot, H. Ross
    - Plimpton, Ruth Talbot, manuscript about Mary Dyer, (3 folders)
    - Politics
    - Population, (1 folder) (Box II:560)
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Freedom of Information Act
      - Gannett v. DePasquale, (2 folders)
      - General
      - Great Britain, (2 folders) (Box II:561)
      - Libel
        - Geneal
        - Immuno AG v. Moor-Jankowskit
      - Pentagon Papers, (3 folders); (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:562, Box II:563)
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Race, (2 folders)
    - Reagan, Ronald See also Classified
    - Refugees
    - Religion
    - Reno, Janet, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:564)
    - Right (political and religious conservatism)
    - Russia, (2 folders)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:565)
    - Secrecy, (2 folders)
    - Speeches
      - Jan. 12-26, (6 folders)
      - Jan. 28 (Box II:566)
      - Mar., (3 folders)
      - Apr. 1-15, (6 folders)
      - Apr. 19-30, (3 folders) (Box II:567)
      - May-Aug., (7 folders)
      - Sept.-Dec., (10 folders) (Box II:568)
    - Supreme Court (Box II:569)
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader
    - Surroundings
    - "S" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - Television, (2 folders) (Box II:570)
    - Thomas, Clarence, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:571)
    - Tobacco
    - "T" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - United Nations
    - "U-V" miscellaneous
    - Wood, Kimba Maureen
    - "W" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Yugoslavia
      - Crimes, (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box II:572)
      - General, (7 folders); (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:573, Box II:574, Box II:575)
      - Owen, David L.
  - 1994
    - Abortion
    - Africa
      - General
      - Mozambique
      - South Africa
        - Elections
        - General
        - Goldstone, Richard, (1 folder) (Box II:576)
        - Law, (3 folders)
        - Trip
        - United States
      - Sudan
      - Zimbabwe Press Mirror, (2 folders)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, (2 folders) (Box II:577)
    - Asia
      - China, (2 folders)
      - India
      - Indonesia
      - Korea (Box II:578)
      - Singapore
      - Vietnam
    - Australia
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Keating, Paul
      - Law, (2 folders) (Box II:579)
      - Trip
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Book reviews
    - Brown, Kathleen
    - Brown, Sam
    - Bylines
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:580)
    - California
    - Capital punishment, (3 folders)
    - Christopher, Warren
    - Clinton, Bill
      - General, (1 folder) (Box II:581)
      - Jones, Paula
      - Whitewater Inquiry, (3 folders)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:582)
    - Congress
    - Constitution
    - Council on Foreign Relations, (2 folders)
    - Crime (Box II:583)
      - General, (4 folders)
      - Habeas corpus
      - Justice Department, Environmental Crime Section, (1 folder) (Box II:584)
    - "C" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Defense, (2 folders)
    - Drugs
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Economy (Box II:585)
    - Education
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Free speech, (3 folders)
    - Fund for Free Expression
    - "F" miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box II:586)
    - Gay rights, (2 folders)
    - Gingrich, Newt
    - Great Britain
      - General
      - Politics
      - Trip
    - Guinier, Lani
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Haiti, (1 folder) (Box II:587)
    - Halperin, Morton H.
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Health, (2 folders)
    - Human rights
      - East Timor, (2 folders)
      - General, (1 folder) (Box II:588)
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Immigration, (3 folders)
    - Indians
    - Inman, Bobby Ray, (3 folders) (Box II:589)
    - Iran
    - Ireland
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Kennedy family
    - "K" miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box II:590)
    - Lake, Anthony
    - Latin America
      - Cuba
      - El Salvador
      - General
      - Guatemala
    - Law (Box II:591)
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Middle East
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Libya
      - Palestine Liberation Organization
      - United States (Box II:592)
      - West Bank
    - "M" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - New York Times
      - Educational television
      - General, (1 folder) (Box II:593)
      - Pulitzer Prize, (2 folders)
      - Staff, (2 folders)
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - Obscenity, (2 folders)
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Politics
      - Election
      - General, (2 folders) (Box II:594)
    - Population, (2 folders)
    - Powell, Colin L.
    - Prayer
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Gannett v. DePasquale, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:595)
      - General
      - Great Britain
      - Libel
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Immuno AG v. Moor-Jankowski
      - Pentagon Papers (Box II:596)
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Race, (6 folders)
    - Religion (Box II:597)
    - Reno, Janet
    - Right
      - Political conservatism, (2 folders)
      - Religious conservatism, (3 folders)
    - Russia, (2 folders)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:598)
    - Secrecy
    - Speeches
      - Feb.-Apr., (6 folders)
      - May-Aug., (7 folders) (Box II:599)
      - Sept., (3 folders) (Box II:600)
      - Oct. 5-9, (3 folders)
      - Oct. 13, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:601)
      - Oct. 14-31
      - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders)
    - Stanford University, Stanford, Calif., Lee Hills Senior Fellowship, (3 folders)
    - Supreme Court (Box II:602)
    - Surroundings
    - "S" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - Television
    - Thomas, Clarence
    - Tobacco
    - "T" miscellaneous (Box II:603)
    - United Nations
    - "V-W" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Yugoslavia
      - Crimes, (3 folders)
      - General, (2 folders); (7 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:604, Box II:605, Box II:606)
      - Humanitas Conference on Former Yugoslavia, Leeds Castle, Great Britain, (2 folders)
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1995
    - Abortion, (2 folders)
    - Africa
      - General
      - Kenya
      - Nigeria
      - Rwanda
      - South Africa (Box II:607)
        - General, (3 folders)
        - Law, (5 folders)
        - Trip, (2 folders) (Box II:608)
      - Zimbabwe
        - General
        - Zimbabwe Press Mirror
    - Aga Khan, IV
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, (3 folders)
    - Arts
    - Asia (Box II:609)
      - Cambodia
      - China, (3 folders)
      - Singapore
      - Taiwan
      - Vietnam, (2 folders)
    - Australia
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - "Bare ruined choirs," regarding Congressional spending cuts of various educational, consumer, and social programs, (2 folders) (Box II:610)
    - Blackmun, Harry A.
    - Book reviews
    - Bylines, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:611)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - California
    - Canada
    - Capital punishment, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:612)
    - Censorship
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - Christopher, Warren
    - Clinton, Bill
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box II:613)
    - Congress
    - Constitution, (2 folders)
    - Council on Foreign Relations
    - Courts
    - Crime (Box II:614)
      - General, (6 folders)
      - Habeas corpus
    - Czechoslovakia
    - "C" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:615)
    - Defense
      - Chemical and biological weapons
      - General
      - Nuclear weapons
    - Dole, Robert J.
    - Drugs, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:616)
    - "D" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Economy, (3 folders)
    - Education
    - "E" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Free speech, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:617)
    - Fund for Free Expression
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Gay rights
    - Gingrich, Newt, (2 folders)
    - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader
    - Gramm, Phil
    - Great Britain
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Trip
    - "G" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:618)
    - Haiti
    - Harvard Magazine
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
      - Black/Jewish Working Group, (2 folders)
      - General
    - Health
    - Human rights
      - East Timor
      - General
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:619)
    - Immigration, (3 folders)
    - Iran
    - Ireland
    - Italy
      - General
      - Trip
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - "K" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:620)
    - Latin America
      - General
      - Guatemala
    - Law, (4 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:621)
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Middle East
      - Egypt
      - General, (1 folder) (Box II:622)
      - Human rights
      - Palestinian Liberation Organization
      - Syria
      - Trip, (2 folders)
      - West Bank
    - "M" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - New York Times
      - Educational television
      - General
      - Reston, James (Box II:623)
      - Staff, (2 folders)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs
    - Nieman Foundation
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Politics
    - Powell, Colin L., (1 folder) (Box II:624)
    - Presidency
    - Press
      - Doder, Dusko, (3 folders)
      - General
      - Great Britain, (2 folders)
      - Libel
        - Australia
        - General, (3 folders) (Box II:625)
        - South Africa
      - Murdoch, Rupert
      - Pentagon Papers, (2 folders)
      - Privacy, (2 folders)
    - "P-Q" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:626)
    - Race, (5 folders)
    - Religion
    - Reno, Janet
    - Right (political and religious conservatism), (1 folder) (Box II:627)
    - Roger Baldwin Medal of Liberty, (2 folders)
    - Russia
    - "R" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Securities Litigation Reform Act
    - Speeches
      - Feb. 1-2, (1 folder) (Box II:628)
      - Feb. 13-28, (3 folders)
      - Mar.-Apr., (5 folders)
      - May 8-22, (2 folders)
      - May 25, (2 folders) (Box II:629)
      - June-Dec., (10 folders)
    - Supreme Court (Box II:630)
      - Breyer, Stephen G.
      - General
    - Surroundings, (4 folders)
    - "S" miscellaneous, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:631)
    - Television, (2 folders)
    - Terrorism
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Law
      - Oklahoma City Federal Building Bombing, Oklahoma City, Okla.
      - Radio
    - Tobacco
    - Turkey (Box II:632)
    - "T" miscellaneous
    - United Nations
    - "U-V" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Waco Branch Davidian Disaster, Tex.
    - Welfare, (3 folders)
    - Wilson, Pete
    - "W" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Yugoslavia (Box II:633)
      - Crimes
      - General
        - 1995
          - Jan.-May, (7 folders)
          - June-Oct., (9 folders) (Box II:634)
          - Nov., (1 folder) (Box II:635)
          - Dec., (2 folders)
      - Peace talks
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - 1996
    - Abortion
    - Afghanistan
    - Africa
      - Kenya
      - South Africa
        - Constitutional Court, decision, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:636)
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Law, (2 folders)
      - Zimbabwe
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:637)
    - Asia
      - Burma
      - China, (2 folders)
      - Hong Kong, (3 folders)
      - Japan (Box II:638)
      - Korea
      - Vietnam
    - Australia
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Book reviews, (3 folders)
    - Brennan Center for Justice, New York, N.Y., (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box II:639)
    - Buchanan, Patrick J.
    - Bylines, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:640)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - California
    - Capital punishment, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:641)
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - Clinton, Bill
      - General
      - Whitewater Inquiry, (5 folders)
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (2 folders) (Box II:642)
    - Congress
    - Constitution
    - Council on Foreign Relations, (2 folders)
    - Courts, (2 folders)
    - Crime
      - General, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:643)
      - Habeas corpus, (2 folders)
    - "C" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Defense
      - General, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:644)
      - Nuclear weapons, (3 folders)
    - Dole, Robert J., (2 folders)
    - Drugs, (3 folders); (9 folders) (Box II:645)
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Ecologically Sustainable Development, Inc.
    - Economy, (4 folders) (Box II:646)
    - Education
    - Europe
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - First Amendment Law Letter
    - Food and Drug Administration, (3 folders)
    - Free speech, (3 folders) (Box II:647)
    - Fund for Free Expression
    - "F" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Gramm, Phil
    - Great Britain
      - General, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:648)
      - Trip
    - Gun control
    - "G" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Harvard Magazine
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
      - Black/Jewish Working Group, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:649)
      - General
    - Health, (2 folders)
    - Human rights
      - East Timor, (2 folders)
      - General, (2 folders)
    - "H" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:650)
    - Immigration, (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:651)
    - Iraq
    - Ireland
    - Italy
      - General
      - Trip
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Kennedy family
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Latin America
      - Cuba
      - General
      - Guatemala, (1 folder) (Box II:652)
      - Peru
    - Law, (4 folders)
    - Limbaugh, Rush H.
    - "L" miscellaneous
    - Massachusetts (Box II:653)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Middle East
      - Egypt
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Lebanon
      - Palestinian Liberation Organization, (2 folders)
      - Syria
      - Trip
    - "M" miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box II:654)
    - New York
    - New York Times
      - General
      - Staff, (2 folders)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs
    - Nieman Foundation
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - Obscenity
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Politics
      - Democratic National Convention
      - General, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:655)
    - Population
    - Powell, Colin L.
    - Press
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Great Britain, (2 folders) (Box II:656)
      - Libel, (2 folders)
      - Pentagon Papers
    - Pulitzer Prize
    - "P-Q" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Race, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:657)
    - Religion, (3 folders)
    - Reno, Janet
    - Right (political and religious conservatism)
    - Russia, (2 folders)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:658)
    - Soros, George
    - Speeches
      - Jan.-Feb., (5 folders)
      - Mar., (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:659)
      - Apr.-Aug., (8 folders)
      - Sept., (3 folders) (Box II:660)
      - Oct., (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:661)
      - Nov.-Dec., (7 folders)
    - Supreme Court (Box II:662)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Thomas, Clarence
    - Surroundings, (3 folders)
    - "S" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:663)
    - Tobacco, (2 folders)
    - Television, (2 folders)
    - Terrorism, (1 folder) (Box II:664)
    - Turkey
    - "T" miscellaneous
    - United Nations, (2 folders)
    - "U-V" miscellaneous
    - Weld, William F.
    - Welfare, (2 folders)
    - Who Cares (Box II:665)
    - "W" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Yugoslavia
      - Crimes, (4 folders)
      - General (Box II:666)
        - Jan.-Aug., (8 folders)
        - Sept., (1 folder) (Box II:667)
        - Oct.-Dec., (4 folders)
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - 1997
    - Abortion
    - Africa
      - Africa News Service
      - Ethiopia
      - Kenya
      - Namibia
      - South Africa (Box II:668)
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Law, (3 folders)
        - Trip, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:669)
        - "Truth"
        - United States
      - Zimbabwe
    - Albright, Madeleine Korbel
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, (4 folders)
    - Asia (Box II:670)
      - China, (2 folders)
      - Indonesia
      - Korea
      - Singapore
    - Australia
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - "Bare ruined choirs," Ishtook amendment
    - Book reviews
    - Brennan Center for Justice, New York, N.Y., (2 folders) (Box II:671)
    - Bylines
      - The Constitution and Its Amendments
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Harvard Law Review, (2 folders)
      - Mandela, Nelson, (1 folder) (Box II:672)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - California
    - Capital punishment, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:673)
    - Censorship
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - Christopher, Warren, (2 folders)
    - Clinton, Bill
      - General
      - PBS documentary about his civil liberties record
      - Whitewater Inquiry, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:674)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (2 folders)
    - Congress
    - Constitution, (4 folders)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box II:675)
    - Courts, (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:676)
    - Crime, (4 folders)
    - Czechoslovakia
    - "C" miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box II:677)
    - Defense
      - General
      - Nuclear weapons
    - Drugs, (3 folders)
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Economy
    - Education
    - "E" miscellaneous (Box II:678)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - First Amendment Law Letter
    - Frankfurter, Felix
    - Free speech, (2 folders)
    - "F" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Gideon's Trumpet
    - Gingrich, Newt
    - Gore, Al
    - Great Britain (Box II:679)
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Police
      - Politics, (2 folders)
      - Trip
    - "G" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Harvard Magazine (Box II:680)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
      - Black/Jewish Working Group
      - General
    - Health
    - Housing
    - Human rights
      - East Timor
      - General
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Immigration
      - General
        - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
        - Mar., (1 folder) (Box II:681)
        - Apr.-Aug., (6 folders)
        - Sept., (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:682)
        - Oct.-Nov., (5 folders)
        - Dec., (3 folders) (Box II:683)
      - Secret, (2 folders)
    - Ireland
    - "I" miscellaneous
    - J. Paul Getty Museum, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - "J" miscellaneous (Box II:684)
    - Kennedy family
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Labor
    - Latin America
      - Cuba
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Guatemala
    - Law, (3 folders)
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Marshall, Thurgood, (2 folders) (Box II:685)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Middle East
      - Egypt
      - General
        - Jan.-Apr., (6 folders)
        - May-Dec., (8 folders) (Box II:686)
      - Kuttab, Daoud
      - Palestinian Liberation Organization
      - Syria
      - West Bank
    - Middlemarch Films
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - New York Times (Box II:687)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Pulitzer Prize submission
      - Staff
      - Sulzberger, Athur Ochs
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - Obscenity
    - Oxford Companion to American Law
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Politics, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:688)
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Race, (3 folders)
    - Religion, (3 folders)
    - Reno, Janet
    - Right (political and religious conservatism)
    - Russia (Box II:689)
    - "R" miscellaneous
    - Secrecy
    - Sheppard, Sam
    - Social security
    - Speeches
      - Jan.-Feb., (4 folders)
      - Mar. 6-17
      - Mar. 20-27, (4 folders) (Box II:690)
      - Apr.
      - May 2-28, (5 folders)
      - May 29 (Box II:691)
      - June, (3 folders)
      - July 24-Aug. 7, (5 folders)
      - Aug. 14-28 (Box II:692)
      - Sept.-Oct., (7 folders)
      - Nov.-Dec., (8 folders) (Box II:693)
    - Supreme Court (Box II:694)
      - General
      - Scalia, Antonin
    - Surroundings
    - "S" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Television
    - Terrorism
    - "T" miscellaneous
    - United Nations
    - "U-V" miscellaneous
    - Weld, William F.
    - Welfare
    - "W" miscellaneous
    - Yugoslavia (Box II:695)
      - Crimes, (2 folders)
      - General, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:696)
      - Trip, (3 folders)
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - 1998
    - Abortion, (2 folders)
    - Africa
      - General
      - South Africa
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, (2 folders) (Box II:697)
    - Asia
      - China, (3 folders)
      - Indonesia
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Baltimore, David, (3 folders) (Box II:698)
    - Book reviews, (2 folders)
    - Boston Globe
    - Brennan Center for Justice, New York, N.Y., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:699)
    - Bylines
      - Courthouse, (2 folders)
      - General
      - King, Martin Luther, Jr., book review
    - "B" miscellaneous
    - Capital punishment, (2 folders)
    - Clinton, Bill (Box II:700)
      - Crisis
        - Briefs, (4 folders)
        - Brill, Steven
        - General, (3 folders); (8 folders) (Box II:701, Box II:702)
        - Press, (2 folders)
      - Foster, Vincent W., (3 folders)
      - General (Box II:703)
      - Impeachment
        - Congress, (6 folders)
        - General, (4 folders) (Box II:704)
        - Starr, Kenneth, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:705)
      - Willey, Kathleen
    - Committee to Protect Journalists
    - Congress
    - Constitution
    - Council for Foreign Relations
    - Courts, (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box II:706)
    - Crime, (2 folders)
    - "C" miscellaneous (Box II:707)
    - Drugs, (5 folders)
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Economy
    - Europe (Box II:708)
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Free speech
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Gideon's Trumpet, (2 folders)
    - Great Britain
    - Guinier, Lani, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:709)
    - "G" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Harvard Magazine